<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<gameList>
  <provider>
    <System>ZX Spectrum</System>
    <software>Skraper</software>
    <database>ScreenScraper.fr</database>
    <web>http://www.screenscraper.fr</web>
  </provider>
  <game id="162924" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Cray-5 (Retroworks).tzx</path>
    <name>Cray 5</name>
    <desc>The game starts when you first enter the main control module of Cray-5. 
 
Once there, you should disconnect the host, and go to the escape pod to return to the main hall. 
 
For safety reasons, the Cray-5 control module is separated from the rest of the ship, cannot be accessed from it, and, moreover, is segmented into 9 watertight levels. 
 
To disconnect the host computer, you should turn off each and every one of the switches scattered in nine zones. In each area you will find a teleporter that may carry you to a variable number of other areas, depending on how many switches you have turned off. 
</desc>
    <rating>0.6</rating>
    <releasedate>20110101T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>RetroWorks</developer>
    <publisher>RetroWorks</publisher>
    <genre>Action-Action / Adventure</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <hash>5718676D</hash>
    <image>./media/images/Cray-5 (Retroworks).png</image>
    <genreid>256</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="162604" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Genesis (Retroworks).tzx</path>
    <name>Genesis - Dawn of a New Day</name>
    <desc>Your mission is quite simple: kill as many enemies as possible, while trying to stay alive. First, you must escape from Earth, to visit five planets and get a part of the Genesis on each one. Once you have successfully assembled the spaceship, you will use it to get back to Earth and free us from the Dork menace. 
 
Your ship has two different shoot types: normal shoot, which will be used to fire the weapons equipped by your ship at any time, and a megablast, which will kill every enemy around you. To activate the megablast, keep the fire button pressed, until the power bar located on the lower-right side of the screen is filled up. The blast will be launched when you release the fire button. You have an unlimited number of normal shoots and a very limited amount of available megablasts, so use them wisely.</desc>
    <rating>0.75</rating>
    <releasedate>20100101T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>RetroWorks</developer>
    <publisher>RetroWorks</publisher>
    <genre>Shoot'em Up-Shoot'em up / Horizontal</genre>
    <hash>982C67A4</hash>
    <image>./media/images/Genesis (Retroworks).png</image>
    <genreid>260</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="164219" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Gommy - Medieval Defender (Retroworks).tap</path>
    <name>Gommy, Defensor Medieval</name>
    <desc>Your mission is to repel the enemy attack dropping objects from the top of the wall. First you must take an object from one of the sides of the screen, aim and drop.  
 
Whatever happens, try at all cost not to let any enemy soldier reach the top of the wall, and don't let any sharp object hit Gommy.</desc>
    <releasedate>20090101T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>RetroWorks</developer>
    <publisher>RetroWorks</publisher>
    <genre>Action</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <hash>C2C41F87</hash>
    <image>./media/images/Gommy - Medieval Defender (Retroworks).png</image>
    <genreid>256</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="163279" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Brunilda (EN) (Retroworks).tzx</path>
    <name>Los Amores de Brunilda</name>
    <desc>The first time I came to this village and met its inhabitants, I realized that something strange was haunting their minds. That evening, the air was so cold that I could even feel it inside my bones. Everybody began to return to their homes, locking their doors tight for the night, hoping not be surprised defenseless against their most horrifying terrors. 
 
It seemed that these people had no soul, that they had turned away from God, abandoned themselves to superstition. 
 
I tried hard to forget that feeling, but my partner could not. He was younger and not yet mastered his terrors. However, my main concern was to find a place to spend the night. I wasn't worried about monsters nor demons, but the cold: another night sleeping rough and my bones would be rankling all the way to Santiago.</desc>
    <rating>0.85</rating>
    <releasedate>20131222T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>RetroWorks</developer>
    <publisher>RetroWorks</publisher>
    <genre>Role playing games</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <hash>6B46C041</hash>
    <image>./media/images/Brunilda (EN) (Retroworks).png</image>
    <genreid>768</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="166434" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Sword Of Ianna (Retroworks).tap</path>
    <name>The Sword of Ianna</name>
    <desc>You are Jarkum, a barbarian from the lineage of Arram. Your ancestor Tukaram was chosen by the goddess Ianna to end the darkness created by Asherat, the Lord of Chaos. Now, everything poitnts to a return of the same evil, although you do not dare to say it aloud to avoid attracting bad luck. However, when an old shaman came to your tent, you knew something was going wrong. 
 
You must leave immediately and go to Kashgar. Evil does not rest, and you are our only hope. Our people, once proud and powerful, has become fearful after all these years of peace, and it won't resist the attack from the forces of Chaos. You must go to Kashgar and listen to your ancestors.</desc>
    <rating>0.9</rating>
    <releasedate>20170101T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>RetroWorks</developer>
    <publisher>RetroWorks</publisher>
    <genre>Action-Action / Adventure</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <hash>448410CC</hash>
    <image>./media/images/Sword Of Ianna (Retroworks).png</image>
    <genreid>256</genreid>
  </game>
</gameList>