<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<gameList>
  <provider>
    <System>Atari 2600</System>
    <software>Skraper</software>
    <database>ScreenScraper.fr</database>
    <web>http://www.screenscraper.fr</web>
  </provider>
  <game id="200014" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./anguna.bin</path>
    <name>Anguna 2600</name>
    <desc>You have been captured by monsters. 
Again? Yes, again. 
How does this keep happening to you? 
This time, you were on a mission to 
kill the evil Goblin King, 
the latest monster to terrorize the land. 
But as usual, somehow you got 
yourself caught by his henchmen. 
Luckily, the monsters aren't any smarter 
this time around. 
If they were any smarter, they would 
have taken your sword away. 
Now you must battle your way 
out of the prison dungeon, 
navigate your way through the land, 
and find and defeat the Goblin King. 
Good Luck!</desc>
    <rating>0.8</rating>
    <releasedate>20150101T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Nathan Tolbert</developer>
    <publisher>Bite The Chili</publisher>
    <genre>Role playing games</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <hash>D18E91A1</hash>
    <image>./media/images/anguna.png</image>
    <genreid>768</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="106808" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./CaveIn230.bin</path>
    <name>Cave In</name>
    <desc>An Adventure type game created by Steve Engelhardt in 2009. 
 
Here are the differences between the three difficulty levels: 
 
Game 1 - Beginner 
Enemies move at normal speed and never have a fast attack 
No health reduction when changing rooms 
Keys are always hidden in the same rooms 
You start out with your gun, and you will never lose it. 
 
Game 2 - Intermediate 
Enemies move at normal speed with occasional fast attacks 
1 point health reduction when you change rooms only after you are down to 3 health blocks left 
Key locations are randomized 
You start out with no gun - you will have to find it, either in the hidden room or dropped by an enemy. 
 
Game 3 - Advanced 
Enemies move at top speed all the time 
1 point health reduction when you change rooms at all times 
Key locations are randomized 
You start out with no gun - you will have to find it, either in the hidden room or dropped by an enemy. 
Falling rocks in the locked caves will fall twice as fast</desc>
    <releasedate>20091223T000000</releasedate>
    <publisher>Spectravision</publisher>
    <hash>9734537E</hash>
    <image>./media/images/CaveIn230.png</image>
  </game>
  <game id="51234" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Halo2600_Final.bin</path>
    <name>Halo 2600</name>
    <desc>The year is 2552. Planet Earth still exists, but overpopulation has forced many of her former residents to colonize other worlds. After contact with an outer colony was lost, a battlegroup was sent to investigate and was almost completely destroyed; only one badly damaged ship returned to tell of a seemingly unstoppable alien warship that had effortlessly annihilated their forces. 
 
This was humankind's first encounter with a group of aliens they eventually came to know as the Covenant, a collective of alien races bent on wiping out humanity. A desperate plan is set in motion: board a Covenant vessel and learn the location of the Covenant home world. But before the mission begins, Covenant forces strike and annihilate the attack force. 
 
The Covenant are now on Earth's doorstep. One ship escapes and makes a blind jump into deep space, hoping to lead the Covenant away from Earth. The ship crashes on Halo--an artificial ring world that is actually a weapon capable of destroying all life in the galaxy should it fall into the hands of the Covenant. 
 
You are the Master Chief--all that remains of a classified military project to build a series of genetically enhanced super- soldiers. You are humanity's last and best hope against the Covenant--but you're woefully out-matched, and survival is not guaranteed. Can you battle your way through the massive world that is Halo, defeat the Covenant, and save humanity?</desc>
    <releasedate>20100731T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Ed Fries</developer>
    <publisher>CGE Services Corporation</publisher>
    <genre>Shoot'em Up</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <hash>3978A823</hash>
    <image>./media/images/Halo2600_Final.png</image>
    <genreid>260</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="200106" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./THE END 2600_PAL60.bin</path>
    <name>The End 2600</name>
    <desc>To destroy aliens attempting to steal bricks from your 3 defense bases. 
The aliens will arrange stolen bricks to spell out "END" at the top of the screen</desc>
    <rating>0.8</rating>
    <releasedate />
    <developer>RaymanC</developer>
    <publisher>RaymanC</publisher>
    <genre>Shoot'em Up-Shoot'em up / Vertical</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <hash>1ABB3A9F</hash>
    <image>./media/images/THE END 2600_PAL60.png</image>
    <genreid>260</genreid>
  </game>
</gameList>